{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.5.5","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1050,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":16,"width":960,"height":540,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_446","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7702","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_1","Text_Caption_446"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7702"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"First Name:   Last Name:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"TEB_First","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"TEB_First","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"TEB_Last","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"TEB_Last","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_195","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29307","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_221","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_447","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_447","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Information_Box_Text_448","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Information_Box_Text_448","title":"Enter your personal information; then click submit. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide29347","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Quiz: Personal Info","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_120","TEB_First","TEB_Last","SmartShape_195","si29307","si29320","Image_221","Text_Caption_447","Information_Box_Text_448"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide29347"}}},{"id":"si62251","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35894","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si35817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Information that a driver needs for an order should be put where so they can see it on the tablet? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35836","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"In Remarks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35832_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In Remarks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35843","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35847","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"In Notes on the Summary Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35843_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In Notes on the Summary Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38698","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"In Notes on the Order Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38698_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In Notes on the Order Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si38713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38717","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"In Notes on the Carrier Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38713_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In Notes on the Carrier Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si35982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35741q0","for":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36001","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35741q0","for":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36018","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide35741q0","for":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: In Notes on the Order Tab ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si35877","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide35741q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide35741","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62251","si62321","si62391","si35817","si35836","si35847","si38702","si38717","si35982","si36001","si36018","si35877"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide35741"},"question":{"interactionId":"35797","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Information that a driver needs for an order should be put where so they can see it on the tablet?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62257","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62325","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62400","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36187","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si36110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Which reference numbers are sent to the driver? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36129","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Stop Level Reference Numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36125_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Stop Level Reference Numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Order Level Reference Numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36136_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Order Level Reference Numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38760","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38764","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Freight Level Reference Numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38760_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Freight Level Reference Numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38775","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38779","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Both A and B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38775_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Both A and B\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si36275","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36034q1","for":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36034q1","for":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36034q1","for":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36157","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: Both A and B ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36170","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36034q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36034","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62257","si62325","si62400","si36110","si36129","si36140","si38764","si38779","si36275","si36294","si36311","si36170"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36034"},"question":{"interactionId":"36090","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which reference numbers are sent to the driver?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62263","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62329","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36480","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si36403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Should you change remarks on an order? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36422","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Yes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36418_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36429","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36433","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"No ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36429_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si36568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36327q2","for":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36587","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36327q2","for":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36604","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36327q2","for":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36437","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36450","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: No ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36463","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36327q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36327","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62263","si62329","si62409","si36403","si36422","si36433","si36568","si36587","si36604","si36463"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36327"},"question":{"interactionId":"36383","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Should you change remarks on an order?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62305","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62472","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38531","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si38454","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The steps you take to force-dispatch are:   Right-click on the order, Select TotalMail, then Select Load Assignment1. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38469","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38469_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38480","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38484","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38480_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38619","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38378q3","for":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38638","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38378q3","for":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38655","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38378q3","for":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: True ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38378q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38378","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62305","si62357","si62472","si38454","si38473","si38484","si38619","si38638","si38655","si38514"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38378"},"question":{"interactionId":"38434","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"The steps you take to force-dispatch are:  \rRight-click on the order, Select TotalMail, then Select Load Assignment1.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62275","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62427","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37066","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si36989","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Activity Start/End times indicate which of the following? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37004","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"When a driver arrives and departs from a location ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37004_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When a driver arrives and departs from a location\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37015","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37019","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The amount of time a driver is moving the tractor ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37015_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The amount of time a driver is moving the tractor\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38794","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The time it takes for a driver to load or unload their trailer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38790_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The time it takes for a driver to load or unload their trailer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si38805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38809","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The times that drivers call in to dispatch ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38805_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The times that drivers call in to dispatch\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36913q4","for":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37173","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36913q4","for":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37190","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36913q4","for":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37036","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: The time it takes for a driver to  load or unload their trailer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37049","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36913q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36913","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62275","si62337","si62427","si36989","si37008","si37019","si38794","si38809","si37154","si37173","si37190","si37049"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36913"},"question":{"interactionId":"36969","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Activity Start/End times indicate which of the following?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62299","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62463","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38238","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si38161","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Error messages must reviewed and addressed quickly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38180","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38176_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38187","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38191","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38187_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38085q5","for":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38085q5","for":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide38085q5","for":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38208","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: True ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38221","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide38085q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide38085","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62299","si62353","si62463","si38161","si38180","si38191","si38326","si38345","si38362","si38221"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide38085"},"question":{"interactionId":"38141","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"Error messages must reviewed and addressed quickly\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62269","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62333","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36773","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si36696","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Black messages in TotalMail represent what?   Select the best answer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36715","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Order updates and errors ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36711_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Order updates and errors\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si36722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36726","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Arrivals and Activity ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36722_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Arrivals and Activity\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38825","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38829","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Messages between dispatchers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38825_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Messages between dispatchers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38840","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Text messages from the driver and informational messages that update TMW ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38840_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Text messages from the driver and informational messages that update TMW\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si36769","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si36861","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36620q6","for":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36620q6","for":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36897","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide36620q6","for":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36743","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: Text messages from the driver and informational messages that update TMW ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si36756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide36620q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide36620","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62269","si62333","si62418","si36696","si36715","si36726","si38829","si38844","si36861","si36880","si36897","si36756"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide36620"},"question":{"interactionId":"36676","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Black messages in TotalMail represent what?  \rSelect the best answer\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62281","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62436","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37359","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si37282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How often should you check you TotalMail Inbox? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37297","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Twice a day ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37297_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twice a day\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the time ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37308_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the time\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si38855","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38859","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"No need to monitor the inbox unless a driver calls ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38855_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No need to monitor the inbox unless a driver calls\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38870","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38874","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Every hour ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38870_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Every hour\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37355","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si37447","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37206q7","for":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37466","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37206q7","for":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37483","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37206q7","for":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37316","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37329","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: All of the time ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37342","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37206q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37206","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62281","si62341","si62436","si37282","si37301","si37312","si38859","si38874","si37447","si37466","si37483","si37342"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37206"},"question":{"interactionId":"37262","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"How often should you check you TotalMail Inbox?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62287","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37652","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si37575","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What format does the driver name need to be in order to search the driver history in TotalMail? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37590","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"First Initial, Last Name ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37590_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"First Initial, Last Name\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37605","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"First Name, Last Name ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37601_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"First Name, Last Name\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38885","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38889","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"By Driver Number ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38885_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"By Driver Number\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38904","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Last Name, First Name ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38900_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Last Name, First Name\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si37648","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si37740","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37499q8","for":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37499q8","for":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37499q8","for":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: Last Name, First Name ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37635","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37499q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37499","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62287","si62345","si62445","si37575","si37594","si37605","si38889","si38904","si37740","si37759","si37776","si37635"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37499"},"question":{"interactionId":"37555","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What format does the driver name need to be in order to search the driver history in TotalMail?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si62293","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62454","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37945","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si37868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How often should you clean out the inbox in TotalMail? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Every few hours ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37883_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Every few hours\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si37894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37898","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"At the end of each load ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37894_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"At the end of each load\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38915","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"At the end of your shift ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38915_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"At the end of your shift\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si38930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continually throughout the day ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38930_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Continually throughout the day\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si38033","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37792q9","for":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38052","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37792q9","for":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si38069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide37792q9","for":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37915","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - the correct answer is: Continually throughout the day ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si37928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide37792q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide37792","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si62293","si62349","si62454","si37868","si37887","si37898","si38919","si38934","si38033","si38052","si38069","si37928"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide37792"},"question":{"interactionId":"37848","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"How often should you clean out the inbox in TotalMail?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_88","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_173","title":"Calculating Results... please wait a moment ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_449","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34198","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_88","Text_Caption_173","Text_Caption_449"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34198"}}},{"id":"Information_Box_Text_175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Information_Box_Text_175","title":"Congratulations, you’ve passed the course! After sending the email, Click X to exit ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_177","title":"Submitting Your Results:   Follow these steps to submit your results if an email does not automatically populate for you:  1) Send an email to: FDG.Dispatch.Training.Results@thekag.com.   2) On the subject line include “VILT Results Dispatcher Training: $$TEB_First$$ $$TEB_Last$$”.  3) In the body include the information from “Your Quiz Results” on the left.  4) Click Send.  You can also regenerate the email with the button on the left.                             ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"Your Quiz Results:   Total Questions:  10 Correct Questions: $$cpQuizInfoTotalCorrectAnswers$$ Maximum Score: 100 Your Score: $$cpQuizInfoPointsscored$$  Final Grade: $$cpInfoPercentage$$% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_222","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_450","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_90","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34507","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34513","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_584","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_584","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62926","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34533","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Information_Box_Text_175","Text_Caption_177","Text_Caption_181","Image_222","Text_Caption_450","Image_90","si34507","si34513","SmartShape_584","si62926","si62953"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34533"}}},{"id":"Image_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_92","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34768","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34774","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Information_Box_Text_183","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Information_Box_Text_183","title":"After reviewing this screen, Click X to exit ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_185","title":"Your Quiz Results:   Total Questions:  13  Correct Questions: $$cpQuizInfoTotalCorrectAnswers$$  Maximum Score: 130  Your Score: $$cpQuizInfoPointsscored$$  Final Grade: $$cpInfoPercentage$$%   $$userMessage$$                            ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_223","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_451","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_451","title":"Interactive Recap for Dispatcher Training ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_453","title":"Email:   Please send the email that has automatically generated on this screen.   If you have already closed the email, press the Generate Email button below to recreate it.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_583","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62823","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si62856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Generate Email ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34801","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_92","si34768","si34774","Information_Box_Text_183","Text_Caption_185","Image_223","Text_Caption_451","Text_Caption_453","SmartShape_583","si62823","si62856"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34801"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Kenan_Quiz","class":"project","title":"Kenan_Quiz","children":["Slide7702","Slide29347","Slide35741","Slide36034","Slide36327","Slide38378","Slide36913","Slide38085","Slide36620","Slide37206","Slide37499","Slide37792","Slide34198","Slide34533","Slide34801"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide35741q0","Slide36034q1","Slide36327q2","Slide38378q3","Slide36913q4","Slide38085q5","Slide36620q6","Slide37206q7","Slide37499q8","Slide37792q9"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":100,"passScore":80}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":true,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7702","title":"Slide 2","visible":true},{"id":"Slide29347","title":"Quiz: Personal Info","visible":true},{"id":"Slide35741","title":"Slide 119","visible":true},{"id":"Slide36034","title":"Slide 120","visible":true},{"id":"Slide36327","title":"Slide 121","visible":true},{"id":"Slide38378","title":"Slide 122","visible":true},{"id":"Slide36913","title":"Slide 123","visible":true},{"id":"Slide38085","title":"Slide 124","visible":true},{"id":"Slide36620","title":"Slide 125","visible":true},{"id":"Slide37206","title":"Slide 126","visible":true},{"id":"Slide37499","title":"Slide 127","visible":true},{"id":"Slide37792","title":"Slide 128","visible":true},{"id":"Slide34198","title":"Slide 129","visible":true},{"id":"Slide34533","title":"Slide 130","visible":true},{"id":"Slide34801","title":"Slide 131","visible":true}]}